<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Delhi Tour</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="site1_name">Lal Quila</string>
    <string name="site2_name">Qutub Minar</string>
    <string name="site4_name">Feroz Shah Kotla</string>
    <string name="site3_name">Humayan\'s Tomb</string>
    <string name="site1_location">Rajpath Area, Raisina Hills, Lal Qila, Old Delhi, New Delhi, Delhi 110011</string>
    <string name="site2_location">Mehrauli, Seth Sarai, Mehrauli, New Delhi, Delhi 110030</string>
    <string name="site3_location">Mathura Road, Opposite Dargah Nizamuddin, Nizamuddin, Nizamuddin East, New Delhi, Delhi 110013</string>
    <string name="site4_location">Balmiki Basti, Vikram Nagar, Vikram Nagar, New Delhi, Delhi 110002</string>
    <string name="site1_hours">Tu - Su | 9:00 AM - 6:00 PM</string>
    <string name="site2_hours">Su - Sa | 7:00 AM - 5:00 PM</string>
    <string name="site3_hours">Su - Sa | 6:00 AM - 6:00 PM</string>
    <string name="site4_hours">Su - Sa | 8:30 AM - 7:30 PM</string>
    <string name="site1_phn_num">+91 99916 47573</string>
    <string name="site2_phn_num">+91 11 2469 8431</string>
    <string name="site3_phn_num">+91 99583 68602</string>
    <string name="site4_phn_num">+91 xxx xxx xxxx</string>
    <string name="site1_desc">The Red Fort is probably Delhi\'s most iconic location.  Built in 1639 by the very industrious and powerful Shah Jahan, who went on to build the Taj Mahal.</string>
    <string name="site2_desc">Qutub Minar is a massive intricately-carved stone edifice erected over a period of several hundred years, beginning in 1192 by Qutab-Ud-Din-Aibak, founder of the Muslim Delhi Sultanate.</string>
    <string name="site3_desc">Equally as impressive and more colorful than the Taj Mahal several hours to the south is the sprawling Humayan\'s Tomb, built in 1569-70 by Mughal emperor Nasir-ud-Din Muḥammad for his wife Bega Begum.  The grounds are host to a number of other tombs that are as equally as impressive.</string>
    <string name="site4_desc">Feroz Shah Kotla is a citadel/city (Ferozabad) that formed part of early Delhi, and was erected by the Muslim Delhi Sultan Feroz Shah Tughlaq in 1354.  One of the curious attractions available at this site is the Topra Ashokan Pillar, one of the few scattered around India.  The Ashokan pillars are inscriptions by various kings encouraging kingdom citizens and future generations in moral, just, and righteous behaviour.</string>
    <string name="restaurants1_name">Karnataka</string>
    <string name="restaurants2_name">Gupta\'s Jelabi Stand</string>
    <string name="restaurants3_name">The Chai Story</string>
    <string name="restaurants4_name">Lodi - The Garden Restaurant</string>
    <string name="restaurants1_location">A-89-90, IGNOU Road, Neb Sarai, Freedom Fighter Colony, Block B, Neb Sarai, Sainik Farm, New Delhi, Delhi 110068, India</string>
    <string name="restaurants2_location">IGNOU Road and Gali No. 3, Neb Sarai, New Delhi, Delhi 110068</string>
    <string name="restaurants3_location">H-30, Middle Cir, Block H, Connaught Place, New Delhi, Delhi 110001, India</string>
    <string name="restaurants4_location">Lodhi Road, Opp. Mausam Bhavan, Lodhi Gardens, Lodhi Estate, New Delhi, Delhi 110003, India</string>
    <string name="restaurants1_hours">Su - Sa | 8:30 AM - 11:00 PM</string>
    <string name="restaurants2_hours">Su - Sa | 7:00 AM - 7:00 PM</string>
    <string name="restaurants3_hours">Su - Sa | 9:30 AM - 11:00 PM</string>
    <string name="restaurants4_hours">Su - Mo | 8:30 AM - 7:30 PM</string>
    <string name="restaurants1_phn_num">+91 11 2953 1641</string>
    <string name="restaurants2_phn_num">+91 8800 305 692</string>
    <string name="restaurants3_phn_num">+91 11 4909 7683</string>
    <string name="restaurants4_phn_num">+91 11 3958 5266</string>
    <string name="restaurants1_desc">North Indian, South Indian, and Chinese cuisine.</string>
    <string name="restaurants2_desc">The best samosas and jalebi, made fresh in Delhi.  Gupta is there during these hours, but samosas start selling at 5 pm on the button.  Given him a few minutes to pray and thank God for the sales of the samosas and jelabi, then the fun begins!</string>
    <string name="restaurants3_desc">The Chai Story is a European-style cafe serving a good variety of chais, cold teas, mojitos, and food.  The pasta and pizza are highly recommended.</string>
    <string name="restaurants4_desc">If high-end European and other world-wide food is your style, try the Garden Restaurant.  This is situated adjacent the Lodi Gardens in the prestigious and beautiful Jor Bagh area, and has amazing food in a quiet and peaceful setting.</string>
    <string name="getting1_name">Indian Railways</string>
    <string name="getting2_name">Gupta\'s Rickshaw Service</string>
    <string name="getting3_name">Redbus.in</string>
    <string name="getting4_name">Jet Airways</string>
    <string name="getting1_location">Federation of Railway Officer\'s Association Office, 256-A, Rail Bhavan, Raisina Road, New Delhi 110001</string>
    <string name="getting2_location">Mehrauli/Badarpur Road, Saket, Delhi</string>
    <string name="getting3_location">E3/8, Block E 3, Jhandewalan Extension, Jhandewalan, New Delhi, Delhi 110005, India</string>
    <string name="getting4_location">Siroya Centre, Sahar Airport Road, Andheri (East), Mumbai - 400099, India.</string>
    <string name="getting1_hours">Mo - Fr | 9:00 AM - 5:30 PM</string>
    <string name="getting2_hours">Su - Sa | 6:00 AM - 9:00 PM</string>
    <string name="getting3_hours">Su - Mo | 12:00 AM - 12:00 AM</string>
    <string name="getting4_hours">Mo - Fr | 9:00 AM - 5:30 PM</string>
    <string name="getting1_phn_num">+91 23389155</string>
    <string name="getting2_phn_num">+91 980 627 5545</string>
    <string name="getting3_phn_num">+91 73689 55410</string>
    <string name="getting4_phn_num">+91 22 6121 1000</string>
    <string name="getting1_desc">Quintessential travel in India.  To not have at least one train experience in India would be almost missing the whole point.  Leaving always on time but rarely arriving as intended, the journey is nonetheless the preferred means of travel:  No traffic.  No horns.  No jackhammers.  No potholes.  No sudden stops and starts.</string>
    <string name="getting2_desc">Almost as iconic as the Indian Railways, a trip to Delhi is incomplete without at least one ride on Gupta\'s rickshaw.  These guys are very cheap, they know the best routes, and can maneuver through gnarly traffic relatively effortlessly.  You will always want to tip these guys because they work extremely hard to get you to your destination.</string>
    <string name="getting3_desc">Redbus has become the default booking app for bus transportation in India.  You can get cheaper, local transportation at the bus stands, but this is a great way to ensure you have a ticket for your next departure or return.</string>
    <string name="getting4_desc">Jet Airways is a home-grown low-cost Indian airline that flies through most major centers in India, and has a significant international presence as well, thanks to contracts with other major carriers.</string>
    <string name="hotels1_name">Smyle Inn</string>
    <string name="hotels2_name">The Leela Palace New Delhi</string>
    <string name="hotels3_name">Golden Tulip Essential</string>
    <string name="hotels4_name">Jugaad Hostels</string>
    <string name="hotels1_location">Chandi Wali Gali, 916 Gali, Main Bazar Rd, Ratan Lal Market, Aram Bagh, Paharganj, New Delhi, Delhi 110055, India</string>
    <string name="hotels2_location">Diplomatic Enclave, Africa Avenue, Chanakyapuri, New Delhi, Delhi 110023, India</string>
    <string name="hotels3_location">Plot No. 1C, Sub District Centre, Hari Nagar, Hari Enclave, Hari Nagar, New Delhi, Delhi 110064, India</string>
    <string name="hotels4_location">Jhandu Mansion, F 128, Mohammadpur, New Delhi, Delhi 110066, India</string>
    <string name="hotels1_hours">Su - Sa | 12:00 AM - 12:00 AM</string>
    <string name="hotels2_hours">Su - Sa | 12:00 AM - 12:00 AM</string>
    <string name="hotels3_hours">Su - Mo | 12:00 AM - 12:00 AM</string>
    <string name="hotels4_hours">Su - Mo | 12:00 AM - 12:00 AM</string>
    <string name="hotels1_phn_num">+91 11 2358 9107</string>
    <string name="hotels2_phn_num">+91 11 3933 1234</string>
    <string name="hotels3_phn_num">+91 11 4083 3333</string>
    <string name="hotels4_phn_num">+91 85100 01800</string>
    <string name="hotels1_desc">The Smyle Inn is a small backpacker hostel in the tourist area of Patparganj.  It has a roof-top restaurant that serves a great breakfast and the staff are very friendly and helpful</string>
    <string name="hotels2_desc">A palatial five-star hotel in south Delhi that will definitely pamper you during your stay in Delhi.</string>
    <string name="hotels3_desc">Located in Nanak Pura in west Delhi, this typical upper-scale but simple hotel offers a complimentary breakfast with room booking.</string>
    <string name="hotels4_desc">Jugaad is a favourite Indian word more or less equivalent to the North American \'duct tape and baling wire\', meaning anything fixed probably has an element of innovation and \'this will hold for awhile\' attitude.  Jugaad Hostels is a very pleasant and fun place for the backpacker crowd.</string>
</resources>
